hillydilly.com 2016-06-21

# Privacy Policy - Hillydilly

Welcome to Hillydilly, a service provided by Hillydilly Media Limited (“Hillydilly”, “we” “our”, “us”).

Your privacy is important to us. This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, store, use, and disclose your information when you use www.hillydilly.com and m.hillydilly.com (together, the “Website”) and our mobile apps (the "Apps").

By using the Website, the Apps, or any of the Services, and, in particular, by registering a Hillydilly account, you are consenting to the use of your information in the manner set out in this Privacy Policy.

If you do not agree to any of the provisions of this Privacy Policy, you should not use the Website, the Apps, or any of the Services. If you have any questions or concerns, you can contact us at support@hillydilly.com.

Please note that this Privacy Policy only applies to the Website and the Apps (together, the “Platform”). When using the Platform, you may find links to other websites, apps, and services. Hillydilly is not responsible for the privacy practices of these other websites, apps, and services.

## Information collection and use

We collect and use your information below to provide our Services and to measure and improve them over time.

**Basic Account information** : When you create or reconfigure an account, you provide some personal information, such as your username, password and email address. On the Hillydilly Platform, the username is listed publicly, including on your profile page and in search results, and you can use either your real name or a pseudonym.

**Additional information:** You may provide us with profile information to make public on the Hillydilly Platform, such as a short biography, your location, your website, or a picture. If you email us, we may keep your message, email address and contact information to respond to your request.

Favorite Tracks, Playlists, Following and other Public information: You may save tracks and playlists to your own list of favorites. You may also create and edit playlists as well as add other users to users you are following. Your profile along with your Favorite tracks, playlists, created playlists and users you are following is public on the Hillydilly Platform.

**Links:** Hillydilly may keep track of how you interact with links across our Services, including our email notifications, and client applications, by redirecting clicks or through other means. We do this to help improve our Services, and to be able to share aggregate click statistics such as how many times a particular link was clicked on.

**Cookies** : Like many websites, we use cookies and similar technologies to collect additional website usage data and to improve our Services, but we do not require cookies for many parts of our Services that don’t require user authentication. A cookie is a small data file that is transferred to your computer or mobile device. We may use both session cookies and persistent cookies to better understand how you interact with our Services, to monitor aggregate usage by our users and web traffic routing on our Services, and to customize and improve our Services. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. You can instruct your browser, by changing its settings, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit.

**Log Data:** When you use our Services, we may receive information (“Log Data”) such as your IP address, browser type, operating system, the referring web page, pages visited, location, your mobile carrier, device information (including device and application IDs), search terms, and cookie information. We receive Log Data when you interact with our Services, for example, when you visit our websites, sign into our Services, use your account to authenticate to a third-party website or application. We may also receive Log Data when you click on, view or interact with links on our Services, including links to third-party applications. Hillydilly uses Log Data to provide, understand, and improve our Services, to make inferences, like what music you may be interested in, and to customize the content we show you.

**Third-Parties and Affiliates** : Hillydilly uses a variety of third-party services to help provide our Services, and to help us understand and improve the use of our Services, such as Google Analytics. These third-party service providers may collect information sent by your browser as part of a web page request, such as cookies or your IP address.

## Information sharing and Disclosure

We do not disclose your private personal information except in the limited circumstances described here.

**Law and Harm** : Notwithstanding anything to the contrary in this Policy, we may preserve or disclose your information if we believe that it is reasonably necessary to comply with a law, regulation, legal process, or governmental request; to protect the safety of any person; to address fraud, security or technical issues; or to protect our rights or property. However, nothing in this Privacy Policy is intended to limit any legal defenses or objections that you may have to a third party’s, including a government’s, request to disclose your information..

## Accessing and Modifying your Personal Information

If you are a registered user of our Platform, we provide you with tools to access, correct, delete, or modify the personal information you provided to us and associated with your account.

You can also permanently delete your Hillydilly account. If you follow the instructions here, your account will be deactivated and then deleted.

Keep in mind that search engines and other third parties may still retain copies of your public information, like your user profile information and public playlists, even after you have deleted the information from the Hillydilly Platform or deactivated your account.

## Our Policy Towards Children

Our Services are not directed to persons under 13. If you become aware that your child has provided us with personal information without your consent, please contact at support@hillydilly.com. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we take steps to remove such information and terminate the child’s account. You can find additional resources for parents and teens.

## Changes to this Policy

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. The most current version of the policy will govern our use of your information and will always be at https://hillydilly.com/privacy. If we make a change to this policy that, in our sole discretion, is material, we will notify you via an email to the email address associated with your account. By continuing to access or use the Services after those changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy.

Effective: August 4, 2015
